=A Love Journal= =Episode 12=
= A Love Journal = = الحلقة 12 =
What kind of friends?
أي نوع من الأصدقاء؟
That depends on you.
هذا يعتمد عليك.
I have something to ask you.
لدي شيء أن أسألك.
You were there that day too,
كنت هناك في ذلك اليوم أيضًا ،
right?
الصحيح؟
Did you go to meet a friend?
هل ذهبت للقاء صديق؟
A man or woman?
رجل ام امرأة؟
Are you asking for Mr. Gu
هل تسأل عن السيد قو
or for yourself?
او لنفسك
Is there a difference?
هناك فرق؟
A man.
رجل.
But,
ولكن،
not my boyfriend.
ليس حبيبي.
I didn't ask that.
أنا لم أطلب ذلك.
I just wanted to tell you
كنت اريد ان اقول لك
I don't have a boyfriend.
ليس لدي صديق.
What a coincidence.
يالها من صدفة.
I don't have a girlfriend.
ليس لدي صديقة.
What day is it today?
ماهو اليوم؟
Why do you invite me to dinner?
لماذا تدعوني للعشاء؟
Today...
اليوم...
I miss you.
أنا افتقدك.
Mom.
أم.
(Why didn't you tell me?)
(لماذا لم تخبرني؟)
Sui.
سوي.
I'm telling you,
أنا أخبرك،
I went shopping today and bought you some gifts.
ذهبت للتسوق اليوم واشتريت لك بعض الهدايا.
So many.
كثير جدا.
Not many.
ليس كثيرا.
I'm telling you,
أنا أخبرك،
when I was shopping,
عندما كنت أتسوق ،
I saw a pair of shoes
رأيت زوج من الأحذية
that fit you very well.
التي تناسبك جيدًا.
Put on them.
ارتديها.
I can't take them, mom.
لا يمكنني أخذهم يا أمي.
Too expensive.
غالي جدا.
Not at all.
لا على الاطلاق.
Just a pair of shoes.
مجرد زوج من الأحذية.
Take them
خذهم
and put them on.
ولبسهم.
Gu Shen.
قو شين.
How do you treat your wife?
كيف تتعامل مع زوجتك؟
Bags, clothes, shoes.
الحقائب والملابس والأحذية.
You didn't buy anything for your wife.
أنت لم تشتري أي شيء لزوجتك.
(Should I accept the shoes or not?)
(هل أقبل الحذاء أم لا؟)
When will you learn to care about your wife?
متى ستتعلم الاهتمام بزوجتك؟
Mom.
أم.
Let's eat first.
دعونا نأكل أولاً.
Right, right.
صحيح صحيح.
Mom.
أم.
Let's eat first.
دعونا نأكل أولاً.
Fine.
بخير.
Here.
هنا.
You sit with Gu Shen.
أنت تجلس مع Gu Shen.
Mom, try this.
أمي ، جربي هذا.
You eat it.
أنت تأكله.
I'm happy if you eat it.
أنا سعيد إذا أكلته.
I'm happy.
أنا سعيد.
Gu Shen.
قو شين.
Serve her some food.
قدمي لها بعض الطعام.
Mrs. Huang.
السيدة هوانغ.
What a coincidence.
يالها من صدفة.
If I hadn't had dinner with my client here,
إذا لم أتناول العشاء مع موكلي هنا ،
I wouldn't have known
لم أكن لأعرف
you have such a relationship with the Gu family.
لديك مثل هذه العلاقة مع عائلة Gu.
Aren't you
لا انت
going to explain it to me,
سأشرحها لي ،
Mrs. Gu?
السّيدة.  ماذا؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
I married Gu Shen,
تزوجت Gu Shen ،
but I always follow the work ethic.
لكني دائما أتبع أخلاقيات العمل.
He doesn't know anything about my job.
إنه لا يعرف أي شيء عن وظيفتي.
Are you joking?
هل تمزح؟
No wonder Canxiang can't fight Liujin.
لا عجب أن Canxiang لا تستطيع محاربة Liujin.
I thought it was because of Manager Sun.
اعتقدت أنه كان بسبب المدير صن.
I didn't expect it.
لم أتوقع ذلك.
I really underestimated you.
أنا حقا قللت من شأنك.
I'm not lying.
انا لا اكذب.
And Gu Shen doesn't know that I'm working for Canxiang.
و Gu Shen لا يعرف أنني أعمل لدى Canxiang.